

GitHub: https://github.com/rushingMarina LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ rushingmarina/

# Marina Pestriacheva

Self-motivated Full Stack Web Developer and a senior computer science student at SDSU. Experience building products for desktop, phone and mobile app users. Working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases. Interested in role with company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

## **Work Experience**

• Magic Ball React App: <a href="https://magicball-app.herokuapp.com/">https://magicball-app.herokuapp.com/</a>

Front End: React, tachyons, react-tilt

Back End: Express.js, bcryptjs, Clarifai API,

Knex, PostgreSQL

Personal web-site: <a href="http://rushingmarina.com/rm-demo/">http://rushingmarina.com/rm-demo/</a>
Built using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap and jQuery

## Math Tutor (10/2017-01/2018) Santa Monica College, Santa Monica

- Provided guidance to students to improve academic performance.
- Backed up teacher instruction by discussing concepts and creating custom practice questions.

### Peer Mentor (05/2017-08/2017) International Education Center, Santa Monica College

- Advised current and potential students on classes, visa issues, and cultural adjustment.
- · Front desk operations.
- · Data entry, phone calls, emails.

## **Education**

## **Bachelor of Science, Computer Science**

San Diego State University (expected to graduate in May 2020)

- · Elected to Web Master position for SDSU Artificial Intelligence Club in 2019
- Coursework in Data Structures with Java, Machine Organization and Assembly language, Combinatorics, Statistical Principles and Practices, Computer Architecture
- 3.65 GPA

## Santa Monica College, (08/2015-06/2018)

- Coursework in C, C++, Java, Calculus, Linear Algebra, Discrete Structures, Ordinary Differential Equations, Critical analysis and intermediate composition and Elements of Public Speaking.
- Dean's Honor List (4 semesters)
- · Member of Alpha Gamma Sigma Honor society member
- Transferred with 3.70 GPA

# Skills

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript(ES6/ ES7/ES8)
- CLI, Git+Github, NPM, React, Bootstrap, jQuery, WordPress, FlexBox
- Java, Python, C, C++, Assembly language for M68000
- HTTP, Node.js, Express.js
- PostgreSQL, SQL
- Operating Systems: Mac OS, Windows
- Microsoft Office
- Data entry

#### **Contacts**

• 333marina2007@gmail.com

San Diego, CA